[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama", "Hillary Clinton"]}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 29, "question": "Are you feeling a little wobbly?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "feeling", "a", "little", "wobbly", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 30, "answer": "Well, you know, Obama was 13 points ahead when Hillary Clinton beat him last time, 13 points ahead the night before.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "Obama", "was", "13", "points", "ahead", "when", "Hillary", "Clinton", "beat", "him", "last", "time", ",", "13", "points", "ahead", "the", "night", "before", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 35, "question": "Would you accept that?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "accept", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 36, "answer": "Well, sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 72, "question": "Well, if I was to put you on the spot now and say who are you supporting, have you got a candidate that now got your eye?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "if", "I", "was", "to", "put", "you", "on", "the", "spot", "now", "and", "say", "who", "are", "you", "supporting", ",", "have", "you", "got", "a", "candidate", "that", "now", "got", "your", "eye", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "CC", "VB", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "RB", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 73, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 96, "question": "Do you think whoever wins the nomination can actually beat Barack Obama, given that the economic climate in America right now appears to be increasing and improving quite markedly?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "whoever", "wins", "the", "nomination", "can", "actually", "beat", "Barack", "Obama", ",", "given", "that", "the", "economic", "climate", "in", "America", "right", "now", "appears", "to", "be", "increasing", "and", "improving", "quite", "markedly", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "CC", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 97, "answer": "It's what I call the Romney effect.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "what", "I", "call", "the", "Romney", "effect", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 118, "question": "How are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 119, "answer": "We're great.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'re", "great", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 147, "question": "Well, we ate a little left baloney growing up, right?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "ate", "a", "little", "left", "baloney", "growing", "up", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "VBG", "RP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 148, "answer": "I'm a big fan of baloney.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "a", "big", "fan", "of", "baloney", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 163, "question": "Has the leopard changed his spots, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "the", "leopard", "changed", "his", "spots", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 164, "answer": "Well, the great news about our father is he is a life- long learner.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "great", "news", "about", "our", "father", "is", "he", "is", "a", "life-", "long", "learner", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "POS", "VBN", ":", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 201, "question": "Why do you say that?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "say", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 202, "answer": "Everything that's been -- now I'm talking about as a candidate.", "answer_tokens": ["Everything", "that", "'s", "been", "--", "now", "I", "'m", "talking", "about", "as", "a", "candidate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "That's what people in that game do, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "what", "people", "in", "that", "game", "do", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 233, "question": "Is he neutral Mitt?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "neutral", "Mitt", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 234, "answer": "No, you rascal, you rascal.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "you", "rascal", ",", "you", "rascal", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 241, "question": "But was it unwise, Jack, in the current climate, with \"Occupy Wall Street\" spreading around America, was he unwise to use a phrase like, \"I like to fire people\"?", "question_tokens": ["But", "was", "it", "unwise", ",", "Jack", ",", "in", "the", "current", "climate", ",", "with", "``", "Occupy", "Wall", "Street", "''", "spreading", "around", "America", ",", "was", "he", "unwise", "to", "use", "a", "phrase", "like", ",", "``", "I", "like", "to", "fire", "people", "''", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "``", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "''", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "Look, he was using it in a totally different context.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", ",", "he", "was", "using", "it", "in", "a", "totally", "different", "context", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jack"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", ":", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 245, "question": "What do you think he meant?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "he", "meant", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": "He was talking about -- about his insurance company that are not taking care of him in his health care problems.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "was", "talking", "about", "--", "about", "his", "insurance", "company", "that", "are", "not", "taking", "care", "of", "him", "in", "his", "health", "care", "problems", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 265, "question": "Why isn't he the one they're all getting behind to take on Obama because at the moment they're not?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "n't", "he", "the", "one", "they", "'re", "all", "getting", "behind", "to", "take", "on", "Obama", "because", "at", "the", "moment", "they", "'re", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "DT", "CD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "IN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "This is early skirmishes.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "is", "early", "skirmishes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Newt Gingrich", "Mitt Romney"], "LOCATION": ["Bain"]}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "NNS", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "WRB", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", ":", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "NN", ",", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 294, "question": "What's the reality behind the myth?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "reality", "behind", "the", "myth", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 295, "answer": "I think that one of the -- when I see these ads by Newt Gingrich talking about how people began to lose their jobs when Mitt Romney came to town, it is such a stark contrast from what it was like to actually work at Bain where there was this incredible sort of -- almost bizarre rah-rah, go business, grow business.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "one", "of", "the", "--", "when", "I", "see", "these", "ads", "by", "Newt", "Gingrich", "talking", "about", "how", "people", "began", "to", "lose", "their", "jobs", "when", "Mitt", "Romney", "came", "to", "town", ",", "it", "is", "such", "a", "stark", "contrast", "from", "what", "it", "was", "like", "to", "actually", "work", "at", "Bain", "where", "there", "was", "this", "incredible", "sort", "of", "--", "almost", "bizarre", "rah-rah", ",", "go", "business", ",", "grow", "business", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 300, "question": "Was he ruthless?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "he", "ruthless", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 301, "answer": "Never in my experience ruthless.", "answer_tokens": ["Never", "in", "my", "experience", "ruthless", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":", "NN", ":", "."], "qSentId": 310, "question": "Why hasn't he already got this wrapped up?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "has", "n't", "he", "already", "got", "this", "wrapped", "up", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "VBN", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "I think we live in a society where you look at him -- I mean it's sort of a weird buys-in (ph).", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "we", "live", "in", "a", "society", "where", "you", "look", "at", "him", "--", "I", "mean", "it", "'s", "sort", "of", "a", "weird", "buys-in", "(", "ph", ")", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "Is it weakness or strength in a leader to do that?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "weakness", "or", "strength", "in", "a", "leader", "to", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "I think it's absolute strength.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "absolute", "strength", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "Is that what you think?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "what", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 353, "question": "Is that true?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 354, "answer": "I don't think so, because they spent it in a different way.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "so", ",", "because", "they", "spent", "it", "in", "a", "different", "way", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 360, "question": "So why should we believe you?", "question_tokens": ["So", "why", "should", "we", "believe", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 361, "answer": "They are going to have to face that.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "are", "going", "to", "have", "to", "face", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "JJR", ":", "IN", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 386, "question": "And when he gets his gander up, he's a very impressive orator as well, isn't he?", "question_tokens": ["And", "when", "he", "gets", "his", "gander", "up", ",", "he", "'s", "a", "very", "impressive", "orator", "as", "well", ",", "is", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 387, "answer": "The problem is we know him more -- as more than a campaigner now.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "problem", "is", "we", "know", "him", "more", "--", "as", "more", "than", "a", "campaigner", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Massachusetts"]}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "But can we drop a little bit of the pious baloney?", "question_tokens": ["But", "can", "we", "drop", "a", "little", "bit", "of", "the", "pious", "baloney", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "Well, if his record was so great as governor of Massachusetts, why didn't he run for re- election.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "if", "his", "record", "was", "so", "great", "as", "governor", "of", "Massachusetts", ",", "why", "did", "n't", "he", "run", "for", "re-", "election", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 424, "question": "Doesn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 425, "answer": "It always has been.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "always", "has", "been", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "VBN", "RP", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 433, "question": "It's so transparent that it actually defeats the whole purpose of saying you can't be involved in these things, doesn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "so", "transparent", "that", "it", "actually", "defeats", "the", "whole", "purpose", "of", "saying", "you", "ca", "n't", "be", "involved", "in", "these", "things", ",", "does", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 434, "answer": "This is what it has all come down to.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "is", "what", "it", "has", "all", "come", "down", "to", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 446, "question": "Do you agree with that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "agree", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 447, "answer": "Part of it.", "answer_tokens": ["Part", "of", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 453, "question": "If you were president right now, what would you be doing?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "were", "president", "right", "now", ",", "what", "would", "you", "be", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "RB", "RB", ",", "WDT", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 454, "answer": "I'd lighten up the regulations.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'d", "lighten", "up", "the", "regulations", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 478, "question": "Is this true?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 479, "answer": "We're back to writing a column again.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'re", "back", "to", "writing", "a", "column", "again", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 487, "question": "Who wears the trousers in this column writing gig?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "wears", "the", "trousers", "in", "this", "column", "writing", "gig", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 488, "answer": "Jack is the idea generator.", "answer_tokens": ["Jack", "is", "the", "idea", "generator", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 493, "question": "Do you argue?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "argue", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 494, "answer": "We have spirited discussions.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "have", "spirited", "discussions", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "CC", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 501, "question": "How did you persuade her to marry you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "persuade", "her", "to", "marry", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 502, "answer": "My charm and probably my wallet.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "charm", "and", "probably", "my", "wallet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 504, "question": "Suzy, is that heartless assessment true?", "question_tokens": ["Suzy", ",", "is", "that", "heartless", "assessment", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "We have just really liked each other a ton.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "have", "just", "really", "liked", "each", "other", "a", "ton", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 508, "question": "Was it 10 years?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "it", "10", "years", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 509, "answer": "Ten years.", "answer_tokens": ["Ten", "years", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 524, "question": "And should it matter anymore?", "question_tokens": ["And", "should", "it", "matter", "anymore", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 525, "answer": "That's a question I'll leave to you to answer.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "a", "question", "I", "'ll", "leave", "to", "you", "to", "answer", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 527, "question": "Suzy?", "question_tokens": ["Suzy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 528, "answer": "Everybody makes mistake.", "answer_tokens": ["Everybody", "makes", "mistake", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["9,000 dollars"]}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 557, "question": "Which one was it, the charm or the wallet?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "one", "was", "it", ",", "the", "charm", "or", "the", "wallet", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "CD", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 558, "answer": "I'm a guy making movies for 9,000 dollars.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "a", "guy", "making", "movies", "for", "9,000", "dollars", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 562, "question": "How did you go about -- why have you done this?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "go", "about", "--", "why", "have", "you", "done", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 563, "answer": "You know, there has been a couple of things that have happened in the last few years.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "there", "has", "been", "a", "couple", "of", "things", "that", "have", "happened", "in", "the", "last", "few", "years", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 599, "question": "How did that work?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "that", "work", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 600, "answer": "I was coming up with the idea for the screen play.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "coming", "up", "with", "the", "idea", "for", "the", "screen", "play", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBG", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 611, "question": "What do you hope -- what's the expectation?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "hope", "--", "what", "'s", "the", "expectation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 612, "answer": "Well, the thing that's amazing is using social media now to publicize the film -- we have done this thing where theatrical doesn't make financial sense for indy films, for the most part.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "thing", "that", "'s", "amazing", "is", "using", "social", "media", "now", "to", "publicize", "the", "film", "--", "we", "have", "done", "this", "thing", "where", "theatrical", "does", "n't", "make", "financial", "sense", "for", "indy", "films", ",", "for", "the", "most", "part", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 619, "question": "And you have already made what, half a million?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "have", "already", "made", "what", ",", "half", "a", "million", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "WP", ",", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 620, "answer": "Just -- I would say a little shy of that.", "answer_tokens": ["Just", "--", "I", "would", "say", "a", "little", "shy", "of", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 661, "question": "Was it in your mind that it might?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "it", "in", "your", "mind", "that", "it", "might", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "."], "aSentId": 662, "answer": "Oh, yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 666, "question": "Do you all hang out together?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "all", "hang", "out", "together", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 667, "answer": "URNS: All the time.", "answer_tokens": ["URNS", ":", "All", "the", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP"], "qSentId": 672, "question": "It was at your wedding?", "question_tokens": ["It", "was", "at", "your", "wedding", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 673, "answer": "It was at our wedding, yes/", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "at", "our", "wedding", ",", "yes/"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 680, "question": "Is being married to Christie Turlington as good as I have always imagined it would be?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "being", "married", "to", "Christie", "Turlington", "as", "good", "as", "I", "have", "always", "imagined", "it", "would", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "VBG", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 681, "answer": "Yes, it is.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "it", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Christie Turlington"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ed Burns"]}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RP", "JJ", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 685, "question": "And she wakes up and looks at me and says, what the hell was I thinking?", "question_tokens": ["And", "she", "wakes", "up", "and", "looks", "at", "me", "and", "says", ",", "what", "the", "hell", "was", "I", "thinking", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "VBZ", ",", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 686, "answer": "She's waking up next to Ed Burns.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "'s", "waking", "up", "next", "to", "Ed", "Burns", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 689, "question": "Life's pretty good, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Life", "'s", "pretty", "good", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 690, "answer": "It's not bad.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "bad", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 693, "question": "Do you have time?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 694, "answer": "I do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Payne"]}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 713, "question": "Wasn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 714, "answer": "You look at all the actors that had the pleasure of working with Payne.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "look", "at", "all", "the", "actors", "that", "had", "the", "pleasure", "of", "working", "with", "Payne", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 718, "question": "Will you be at the Golden Globes?", "question_tokens": ["Will", "you", "be", "at", "the", "Golden", "Globes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 719, "answer": "I will not, no.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "will", "not", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 720, "question": "So you'll be avoiding the Ricky Gervais roast?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "'ll", "be", "avoiding", "the", "Ricky", "Gervais", "roast", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 721, "answer": "Oh, yeah, yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yeah", ",", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ricky Gervais"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 723, "question": "Do you laugh as loudly as I do at the sheer amount of offense he causes?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "laugh", "as", "loudly", "as", "I", "do", "at", "the", "sheer", "amount", "of", "offense", "he", "causes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 724, "answer": "I just absolutely love it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "just", "absolutely", "love", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 741, "question": "Could you take it?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "you", "take", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 742, "answer": "I think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]